迈克:我不能呆在这里了,
Mike: Baby, I can't stay here and neither can you.
你也不能!
I mean, for once in our miserable lives we've got a chance at something good.
我的意思是在我悲惨的时刻我们有机会在一起面对幸运,谁知道这是我们唯一的机会的.
And who knows this could be the only shot we ever get!
所以我们再试一次!
So, we've got to try.
本:还得再来一次!
Ben: We gotta do it again, Mike.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
本:迈克,为什么?
Ben: You were looking right into the camera!What do you think you're doing?
你说话时总盯着镜头,就像什么是做报告.
Moonlighting?
迈克:本拍这个是为了我明天面试能自然一些.
Mike: Look, Ben, this tape is for me so I can do a better audition
tomorrow, alright
本:好吧,不过迈克·福克斯拍片子的时候,
Ben: Ok.But all I'm saying is you never see Michael J.
从来不看镜头的.
Fox look into the camera.
迈克:听着,等莫妮卡来了,
Mike: Look, when Monica gets here I won't look into the camera,
我就不再看镜头了,我盯着她你别停.
I'll look at her.Just keep shooting.
本:迈克要是我问你一个姑娘问题,
Ben: Mike, if I ask you a question about girls will you tell everybody
你会说出去让人家笑我吗?
so they laugh at me?
迈克:姑娘?不,不,好吧,好吧,你问吧,我保证不讲.
Mike: Girls, huh?No, no, no.Ok, alright.The play can wait.Ok, ask away.
本:那好,我们班上新来了一个女同学,
Ben: Ok.Well, there's this new girl at school and she's the only girl
我们全班女生里只有她戴胸罩.
in my class who wears a bra.
我每次见到她就会全身冒汗说蠢话,
Every time I see her I start sweating and saying dumb stuff.
有时我想吻她,又想揍她.
I either want to kiss her or slug her.
迈克:好吧,可以吻,但不能揍.
Mike: Always kiss, never slug.
本:要是我吻了她,她揍我呢?
Ben: What if I do kiss her and she slugs me?
迈克:生活里只要遇到好机会,
Mike: Well, Ben there's comes a time in your life when you gotta take
就得抓住懂吗?我是说你想吻她,
a chance, you know?
就不能整天玩这个大兵.
I mean, at some point you're gonna have to stop playing with G.I.Joe.
本:也许我该揍她.
Ben: Maybe I'll just slug her.
莫妮卡:嗨迈克.
Monica: Hi, Mike.
迈克:哦,这不行亲爱的,
Mike: Oh it's no use, baby.
我太窝囊了,像我这种人到哪儿也没有出路.
I'm just a bum and there's no place in the world for a guy like me.
莫妮卡:哦,
Monica: Oh, I think you're very entertaining.
我觉得你很讨人喜欢,你还经常讲各种俏皮话,
I mean, I think you say all sorts of witty things.
你跳舞也跳得很好.
And you are a wonderful dancer.
迈克:嗨,怎么样?
Mike: Hey!How's it going?
莫妮卡:哦迈克,一定会让我们演的,
Monica: Mike!We are going to get these parts, I can feel it!
我有把握,
We are going to make this production of Picnic the best thing Dewey High
上次我们演小镇就很成功,这次演野餐也一定会造成极大轰动.
has ever seen since we did Our Town.
迈克:现在还不该吹.
Mike: Well, we shouldn't brag.
莫妮卡:上次演小镇不是很成功吗?
Monica: You don't think we were a smash in Our Town?
迈克:当然很成功,但不该吹.
Mike: Well, of course I do, but we shouldn't brag.
莫妮卡:我敢打赌,他们在林肯中心演的,
Monica: I bet that production at Lincoln Center won't be half as good
一定比我们演的还差.
as the one we do.
迈克:演什么?
Mike: What production?
莫妮卡:信息报上登了你没看?
Monica: You didn't read about it in Variety?
迈克:没有,这期还没看.
Mike: Uh, no.I must have missed that issue.
莫妮卡:哦,在这儿,
Monica: It's right here.
百老汇大剧院今年夏天将上演名剧小镇.
The first Broadway production of Our Town to open in twenty years.
迈克:真的.
Mike: Oh, really?
莫妮卡:我们拍野餐吧,
Monica: Come on, let's get back to picnic.
我看是不是从……
Why don't we start out with the scene...
Mike: Wait a minute, Monica.Why do we want to do another high school play
莫妮卡:什么?
Monica: What?
迈克:我们干嘛不去试试这个呢?
Mike: Why don't we audition for this?
莫妮卡:百老汇?Mike那可是第一流的.
Monica: Broadway?Mike, that's the big time.
迈克:不行吗?
Mike: Exactly!
莫妮卡:迈克怎么能从杜威中学一下跳到百老汇?
Monica: Mike!How do you expect to go from Dewey High to Broadway?
迈克:没事,我有车.
Mike: I was gonna drive.
莫妮卡:去百老汇面试,可不像在学校里面试.
Monica: Broadway is not like trying out for a high school play.
迈克:还不是一样念台词给他们听.
Mike: What, you don't go in and read the part for these people?
莫妮卡:当然是的,可是在那听得的人并不是老师,
Monica: Well, sure you do.But the people you're reading for aren't teachers.
他们都是专家.
They know what they're doing.
迈克:莫妮卡你不是一直想见专家吗?
Mike: Monica, isn't this what you've always dreamed about?
莫妮卡:哦,对,不错,是的,想见.
Monica: Well, yea, sure.But yea it is.
迈克:我也想,那次在学校演,
Mike: Well, me too.
我的自我感觉很好,
I mean I know what it felt like to be in that play at Dewey,
感到很有前途懂吗?我的才能应该充分发挥,
to be good at something, you know?And I want to have that feeling again.
而且是在大剧院,
But in a real theatre.And you said it yourself, we're the best!
你自己也说过我们最棒,把报上的评论给他们看.
I mean, we can show them our reviews.
莫妮卡:那张杜威戏迷报.
Monica: From the Dewey Hooter Press?
迈克:哦,行了,你可别这样,你也很想去的.
Mike: Oh, come on.You don't fool me.You love this idea!
莫妮卡:迈克百老汇剧院明天就要面试,
Monica: Mike, the auditions in New York are tomorrow.
我们学校的面试也是在明天.
The same day as tryouts for Picnic at school.
迈克:莫妮卡我们就不去学校了,
Mike: Monica, we're not gonna audition for both.
百老汇的演员怎么能到学校来演戏,
I mean, how can we be in the Dewey play when we're starring on Broadway?
现实一点.
Be realistic.
莫妮卡:那就得翘课了.
Monica: But we have to cut school.
迈克:你过去就没有,就没有上过台吗?嗨爸爸.
Mike: So what?You never cut yourself shaving before?Oh, Hi Dad!
杰森:嗨迈克,莫妮卡很高兴见到你.
Jason: Hi, Mike.Hello, Monica.Nice to see you again.
莫妮卡:我也是西维尔医生.
Monica: You too, Dr.Seaver.
迈克:好了,别担心,
Mike: Ok, so where were we?Oh, yea.
我说你一定能够被录取的.
You were convincing me to try out for this.
莫妮卡:迈克我怕.
Monica: Mike, I'm scared.
迈克:哦,你听着,咱俩一起去,我这个笨蛋都不怕,你看怎么样?
Mike: Oh, well, look, you'll be with me and I'm too dumb to be scared
So, what do you say
莫妮卡:我同意.
Monica: You're right.
迈克:好,同意去百老汇,还是同意我是笨蛋?
Mike: Yea!About going to Broadway or about me being dumb?
本:爸爸,为什么我不能同时喜欢大兵和姑娘呢?
Ben: Dad?Is there any reason why I can't like girls and soldiers?
杰森:你说呢?什么?
Jason: No.What?
本:没什么,再见了.
Ben: Never mind.See you later!
杰森:本,在学校里要好好的.
Jason: Hey, Ben.Have a nice day at school.
麦琪:本呢,他们校车来了.
Maggie: Where's Ben?His bus is at the corner.
杰森:他刚走.本认识大兵吗?
Jason: He just left.Does Ben know any soldiers?
麦琪:不.
Maggie: No.
杰森:我想也是,好.
Jason: I didn't think so.Good.
麦琪:他连奶油松饼都没吃完.
Maggie: He didn't even touch his Fudge Flakes.
迈克:早上好.
Mike: Morning.
麦琪:嗨!微波炉里有火腿煎鸡蛋和……哇,
Maggie: Hi!There's scrambled eggs in the microwave and, uh, oh,
干嘛穿得这么漂亮?
why are you so dressed up?
迈克:我是.
Mike: Well, I, uh...
杰森:又想翘课了.
Jason: Cutting school today?
迈克:爸爸你别这么讲.
Mike: You know, Dad, that really hurts.
你瞧,
You know, I mean,
你让我行为规矩,衣着整洁,
all I try to do is follow your advice about cleaning up my act and you
我做了你倒怀疑起我来了.
get suspicious.
杰森:怎么说呢,是我不好.
Jason: What can I say?I'm scum.
迈克:没关系,
Mike: It's ok.I mean,
你说我做什么才能使你们相信,
what else can I do to convince you people that I can be trusted and be
我这个人很可靠.
depended on?
麦琪:那么今天你就送你妹妹去看医生.
Maggie: Well, you could give your sister a ride to the doctor today.
迈克:她是不是得神经病了.
Mike: What, is she due for her next rabies shot?
开萝尔:迈克我听见了.
Carol: I heard that!
杰森:迈克你刚才对我们说,
Jason: Mike, you said that you were trying to convince us that you could
你让我们相信你这个人很可靠?
be dependable and trustworthy.
迈克:是这样的.
Mike: You're right.
麦琪:你妹妹要你送她去看妇科.
Maggie: Your sister needs a ride to her gynecologist.
开萝尔:这是怎么回事,
Carol: Oh, what's the matter, Mike?
迈克你一听到妇科就紧张.
Does the word gynecologist make you nervous?
迈克:妈妈让她别讲了.
Mike: Oh, Mom, make her stop.
麦琪:迈克你爸爸和我今天没空,
Maggie: Mike, your dad and I are both busy today.
你放了学能否送Carol去?
Now, can you take her after school or not?
迈克:啊,要知道我今天在学校里要演戏.
Mike: Um, well, see, we have the auditions for the senior play today.
杰森:演戏你可不能不去.
Jason: Oh, wow.Yea, you sure don't want to miss those.
迈克:对,今天要面试.
Mike: Yea.They're today.
麦琪:所以你穿得特别整齐.
Maggie: Well, that's why you're so dressed up.
迈克:对,很对.
Mike: Yup, that's why.
麦琪:我们不希望你错过面试机会.
Maggie: Well, we sure don't expect you to miss the auditions.
迈克:谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
麦琪:你可以面试完了送她去.
Maggie: You can take her after the auditions.
迈克:还要去?
Mike: After?
开萝尔:你干嘛不愿意送我去?
Carol: But, why can't you take me?
迈克:我不能说.
Mike: I can't say.
开萝尔:哦,你是不是怕我告诉去爸爸妈妈呢?
Carol: Oh, and you expect me not to tell Mom and Dad about this?
迈克:你跟同学看黄色电影,我都没告诉他们.
Mike: Hey, I didn't tell them when you and your friend rented that dirty movie.
开萝尔:那可是艺术电影.
Carol: It was an art film.
迈克:对,那里面的主角叫艺术.
Mike: Yea, the guy in the mask was named Art.
开萝尔:你怎么知道的?
Carol: How do you know about that?
迈克:开萝尔我什么都知道,
Mike: Carol, I know everything, alright?
懂吗?你能否自己去找医生,
Now can't you find another way to your doctor and not say anything to
而不跟爸爸妈妈漏一个字.
Mom and Dad?
开萝尔:可你得讲清原因.
Carol: But you won't tell me why.
迈克:可以说我今天很有可能要实现自己的梦想.
Mike: Let's just say that today I have a chance to make a dream come true.
开萝尔:哦,这跟那个新来的瑞典女生,是否有什么关系?
Carol: Oh, this doesn't have anything to do with that Swedish exchange student.
迈克:没有.
Mike: No.
开萝尔:好吧,我替你瞒着.
Carol: Alright, I'll cover for you.
迈克:那好,谢谢Carol.
Mike: Alright, thanks Carol!
开萝尔:可是至少你得跟我讲明白.
Carol: But the least you could do is tell me what you're doing.
迈克:好吧,我跟你讲今天莫妮卡和我要去曼哈顿,
Mike: Ok, alright.Here it is.
到百老汇去参加面试.
Today, Monica and I are going into Manhattan to audition for a Broadway play.
开萝尔:哦好了,别再讲下去了.
Carol: Oh, fine.Don't tell me then!
广播:同学们注意,下面几位同学请立刻到大礼堂来报道,
Intercom: Attention, people.The following students are to report to the
莫妮卡·希克福德.哦,
auditorium immediately.Monica Shakelford.
真想不到.迈克·西维尔上就来.
Oh, this is a big surprise, Michael Seaver.And I mean pronto.
莫妮卡:喂?迈克.
Monica: Hello?Mike?
迈克:莫妮卡嗨,这是我们演小镇时穿的服装,
Mike: Monica, hi!Look, look at what I got!
就穿这个去面试.
These are the costumes from Our Town.We can audition in these.
莫妮卡:我们逃学的事会给他们知道的.
Monica: Somehow they find out we were going to cut school.
迈克:不会的.
Mike: No, they didn't.
莫妮卡:会的,你没听校长在广播里喊我们?
Monica: They did.Didn't you hear the principal call our name's over the loud speaker
迈克:真是想不到迈克·西维尔.
Mike: And here's a real surprise, Michael Seaver.
莫妮卡:Mike你跟他的声音太像了.
Monica: Mike!That sounds exactly like him!
迈克:对,
Mike: Yea, thanks.All the teachers heard that, too.
所有老师都听见了,我们不去上课,
So when we don't show up for classes,
老师还以为校长在罚我们.
they'll just figure that we're being punished.
莫妮卡:我看不行迈克,老师哪有那么笨?
Monica: It won't work, Mike.Teachers aren't that stupid.
教练:好啊迈克,什么事被校长抓住了?
Coach Luvok: Well, ok, Seaver.What did DeWitt catch you doing now?
迈克:哦,卢沃克教练,嗨.
Mike: Coach Luvok, Hi.
卢沃克教练:别来这一套了.
Coach Luvok: Don't give me that.
听着今天面试野餐你们俩都得参加,
Now, look, I need both of you in my production of Picnic.
要是校长的处罚影响你们今天的面试.
So, if this punishment is going to interfere with the tryouts today
迈克:别着!别着!
Mike: Oh, it won't.It won't.
教练:好,我全靠你们俩了,
Coach Luvok: Good.I'm counting on both of you,
上学期你们俩演出小镇这部戏,
cause what you did last semester in Our Town,
那是我们戏剧艺术历史上的里程碑,我得上厕所了.
was a milestone in the history of dramatic art.I gotta go to the can.
莫妮卡:他说的你都听见了.
Monica: Mike, did you hear what he said?
迈克:对,是戏剧艺术历史上的里程碑.
Mike: Yea, a milestone in the history of dramatic art.We can't miss!
莫妮卡:迈克错了,
Monica: Mike, Mike, no.
卢沃克教练是指望着我们俩,
Coach Luvok is counting on us to be here and if we don't show we're going
我们不上场会有大麻烦的.
to get in trouble.
迈克:莫妮卡想象一下,
Mike: Monica, just imagine.
林肯中心将上演小镇,
Lincoln Center presents Our Town,
主演迈克·西维尔和莫妮卡·希克福德.
starring Michael Seaver and Monica Shakelford.
莫妮卡:能不能说成莫妮卡·希克福德和迈克·西维尔主演.
Monica: How about starring Monica Shakelford and Mike Seaver.
迈克:可以商量.
Mike: We can talk.
迈克:主演迈克·西维尔,应该这样,
Mike: Starring Mike Seaver!No, Michael Seaver.
主演迈克·J·西维尔,这样还可以.
No, I got it, starring Michael J.Seaver.It's almost right.
莫妮卡:我给你想了一个很好的艺名.
Monica: I've got the perfect stage name for you!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
莫妮卡:汤姆·西维尔!
Monica: Tom Seaver!
迈克:汤姆·西维尔?
Mike: Tom Seaver?
莫妮卡:对,好像很响亮的.
Monica: Yea!It just sounds famous!
迈克:是很响亮,是个很棒的球手.
Mike: It is famous.He's a great pitcher.
莫妮卡:哦,那你不能用了.
Monica: Oh, so you can't use it?
迈克:你打算起一个什么艺名吗?
Mike: Um, look, ok.What are you going to use for your stage name?
莫妮卡:我有你听着,莫妮卡·迪塞蒙,
Monica: Ok, are you ready?Monique Desemone.
听上去是不是有那么一点法国味道?
Doesn't that just sound exotic and French?
迈克:有.
Mike: Yea.
莫妮卡:你念念.
Monica: Say it!
迈克:莫妮卡·迪塞蒙.
Mike: Ok.Monique Desemone.
莫妮卡:我喜欢.
Monica: Oh!I like it!
迈克:可是我不会讲法语.
Mike: And I don't even speak French!
莫妮卡:哦,听着,我真想明晚都能上大戏院演出,
Monica: I can't wait to be going to the theatre every night,
全身穿着戏装,站在舞台上频频谢幕,然后上大酒店吃夜宵.
putting on our makeup, and then after standing ovations, going to soirees
迈克:我们就,哦,
Mike: Yea, then we can Oh, wait a minute.
得回家了,我11点不到家要受罚的.
You know, if I'm not home by eleven, I'll be grounded.
莫妮卡:我姐姐有个朋友就在这儿附近,
Monica: My sister has a friend who lives in the Village.
他会让我们住下的.
I bet we could stay with her!
迈克:哦,好.
Mike: Oh, yea!
Monica: I can't believe this!Monica Shakelford on her way to Broadway
迈克:不,莫妮卡·迪塞蒙正在走向百老汇.
Mike: No, Monique Desemone is on her way to Broadway!
迈克:我说莫妮卡我真高兴能到这儿来,你面试绝不能紧张,
Mike: You know, Monica, I'm really glad we're here together and you know,
该这样想,
you don't have to be nervous, I mean, look at it this way.
你终于找到了归宿,找到了施展才能的地方.
You're finally where you belong, getting a chance to do what you do best.
女士:祝你成功.
Lady: Break a leg.
莫妮卡:嘿,你非常不错.
Monica: Hey, Mike!You look great.
迈克:好,我们俩都不错,走吧.
Mike: Yea, we both look great, ok?Come on.
莫妮卡:嗨你瞧这.
Monica: Hey, Look at this!
迈克:对,你瞧,这是顾客里的那个爱丽丝.
Mike: Oh, yea!Look that's Alice from Mel's Diner.
莫妮卡:琳达·瑞维哲她刚得了最佳女演员奖.
Monica: Linda Ravage!She just won a Tony as best actress!
迈克:对,这就是那个犯罪学专家.
Mike: Yea and that old chick that solves all the crimes!
莫妮卡:安吉拉·兰斯伯瑞还有玛丽·马丁,克里斯托福· 普拉莫,
Monica: Angela Lansbury!Then there's Mary Martin!Christopher Plummer!
德斯汀· 霍夫曼.
Dustin Hoffman!
迈克:哦,那是女神伊师塔,我爱那部片子.
Mike: Oh, yea!From Ishtar!I love that movie!
莫妮卡:迈克要是没有你,我是不会上这儿来的,谢谢你.
Monica: Mike, if it weren't for you, I wouldn't be here right now.Thanks.
迈克:不妨以后再谢我.
Mike: Well, you can thank me later.
莫妮卡:这些明星可是全从这儿成长起来的.
Monica: All these people must've auditioned in this building.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yea.
莫妮卡:迈克我有点紧张.
Monica: I think I'm starting to get nervous.
迈克:你听着只要深吸一口气就会好的,你一定要记住,
Mike: Hey, look!Alright!Just take a deep breath and you'll be ok.Alright?
我们最棒,谁也比不上我们.
And remember, we're the best!There's nobody like us!
莫妮卡:对,我们最棒,谁也比不上我们.
Monica: Right.We're the best!There's nobody like us!
莫妮卡:谁也比不上我们?
Monica: There's nobody like us?
接待员:亲爱的.
Receptionist: Yoo-hoo!Sweetie!
迈克:嗨,我们俩是来面试小镇的.
Mike: Uh, hi.We're here to audition for Our Town.
接待员:好吧,亲爱的先填表,
Receptionist: Ok, sweetie.Fill out these forms.
填清楚经纪人或代理人,单位和家里电话,
Be sure to list your agent and/or manager, day phone, night phone,
属于什么工会,还有两张照片.
union affiliation, and I'm gonna need pictures.
迈克:你哪来的?
Mike: Where'd you get that?
莫妮卡:我每年都拍,用得着的.
Monica: I have a set done every year, just in case.
接待员:好,你的.
Receptionist: And you?
迈克:有,有,当然有,有,没问题.
Mike: Uh, yea.Um Oh, yea!Here, sure.No problem.
接待员:是你的驾驶执照.
Receptionist: Your driver's license?
迈克:对,是的,不仅演戏,我还得开车.
Mike: Yea, well, hey.I don't just act.I drive, too.
莫妮卡:112号.
Monica: 112?
接待员:16号过来.
Receptionist: Number sixteen.
迈克:有这么多人你想到过没有?
Mike: Whoa, did you have any idea there would be this many people?
莫妮卡:我,当然,面试都是这样的.
Monica: Oh, sure.All auditions are this way.
迈克:哦.
Mike: Oh.
莫妮卡:怎么你想走了.
Monica: Why?Did you want to leave?
迈克:不,不,难道你想走.
Mike: Uh, no, no.Why?Did you want to leave?
莫妮卡:不,怎么可能.
Monica: No!Not at all.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yea.I mean,
我在想这究竟有多少人,曾经演出过小镇而获得了极大的成功,
how many of this people could have just finished a standing room only
真的.
production of Our Town?Really?
莫妮卡:谢谢,请把手都放下来.
Monica; Uh, thank you.You can put your hands down.
本:你自己也在那玩大兵?
Ben: So you do play with G.I.Joe.
杰森:本我只是在……本你的眼睛怎么了?
Jason: Now, Ben, I was just, uh Ben!What happened to your eye?
本:连我自己也没弄懂.
Ben: That's what I'd like to know.
杰森:你是不是跟谁打架了?
Jason: You get in a fight with somebody?
本:我没打架,是吻了一个人.
Ben: No, I kissed somebody.
麦琪:嗨,亲爱的.嗨,本.
Maggie: Hi, honey.Hi, Ben.
杰森:你瞧.
Jason: Look.
麦琪:哦,你眼睛怎么了?
Maggie: What happened to your eye?
杰森:他吻了一个人.
Jason: He kissed someone.
麦琪:我来给你放上点冰.
Maggie: I'll put some ice on it.
杰森:喂卢沃克教练,请你轻一点,你别喊,不,迈克不在,我以为他去学校面试了.
Jason: Hello?Yes, Coach Luvock, Hi.Whoa, whoa, settle Calm down, wait.You're shouting!No
Mike's not here.No, we thought that he was at your auditions
开萝尔:嗨,各位.
Carol: Hi, everybody!
杰森:你等一下.开萝尔,迈克面试前送你去看医生了?
Jason: Just a sec.Carol, did Mike take you to the doctor before auditions?
开萝尔:迈克?我明天有考试,我还得去拼命呢.
Carol: Mike?Well, I have to go cram for a test, so, uh...
杰森:你用不着去拼命,姑娘.
Jason: You're not cramming anything, young lady.
不,谢谢莉德亚.我会去替你向德斯汀问好的,
Actor: No, no, thank you, Lydia.I'll be sure to say hello to Dustin for you.
他要找我,我今晚就得飞海岸,再见.
Now if he needs me, I'm winging to the coast tonight.Ciao.
莫妮卡:迈克我有点不明白.
Monica: Mike, I'm not sure about this.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
莫妮卡:他们都得要飞海岸.
Monica: These people wing to the coast.
迈克:怎么了?我们不用飞,我们家离海岸才十米.
Mike: So, what?We don't need to wing, we live ten miles from the coast.
莫妮卡:不,是西海岸,是好莱坞,他是说全世界的电影中心.
Monica: No.The west coast?Hollywood?The motion picture capital of the world?
迈克:哦,哦对.
Mike: Oh.Oh, yea.
莫妮卡:看那个人,他只是拍胸罩广告.
Monica: That guy over there, he does underwear commercials.
迈克:哦,对,等一下, 香蕉还是葡萄?
Mike: Oh, yea.Oh, wait a minute.Is he the Banana or the Grapes?
莫妮卡:迈克这都是些专业演员,
Monica: Mike these people are trained professionals.
我们没有什么经纪之类的.
We don't have agents or credits or...
接待员:111号.
Receptionist: Number one eleven.
迈克:好了,下一个就是.
Mike: Ok, we're next.
莫妮卡:我想出去一下.
Monica: I got to get out of here.
迈克:莫妮卡你.
Mike: Monica!
接待员:等一下,祝你们下一次走运,
Receptionist: Better luck next time sweetie.Oh!
哦,别忘了驾驶执照.
Don't forget your driver's license.
迈克:不,我们不走,
Mike: Uh, no, no.We're not leaving.
我们是去上女厕所.莫妮卡,
We're just, um, merely going to the ladies room.Monica!
哦,你非上厕所不可.
You do have to go to the bathroom!Oh!
莫妮卡:哦,不是的.
Monica: No, I don't.
迈克:什么意思?
Mike: What do you mean?
莫妮卡:迈克今天来这儿,这是我的梦想.
Monica: Mike, all of this.This is my dream.
迈克:对,我和你一样.
Mike: Yea, I know!It's mine, too.
莫妮卡:所以我不愿意打破我的梦境.
Monica: So, I don't want anything to happen to it!
迈克:所以你要离开?
Mike: So, you want to leave?
莫妮卡:是的.
Monica: Yes.
迈克:莫妮卡要是梦想不能实现,这还有什么意思?
Mike: Monica, what good is a dream if you're not gonna do anything about it?
接待员:112号.
Receptionist: Number one twelve.
迈克:快点,轮到我们了.
Mike: Alright, come on.We're next!
莫妮卡:迈克我们是在骗自己,我们俩根本不行.
Monica: Mike!We're kidding ourselves.We're not ready for this!
迈克:行不行试了以后才能知道.
Mike: We're never gonna know if we don't go through with it.
莫妮卡:我可不想去试.
Monica: Well, I don't want to know.
接待员:112号,最后一遍.
Receptionist: One twelve!Last call!
迈克:小心点德斯汀,112号.
Mike: Look out, Dustin.Number one twelve!
麦琪:他去参加百老汇的面试?纯粹胡闹.
Maggie: Auditioning for a Broadway play?That's ridiculous!
开萝尔:是他说的.
Carol: That's what he said!
杰森:Carol你认为我们会相信你?
Jason: Carol, you expect us to believe that?
开萝尔:不,不会相信.
Carol: No, I don't.
麦琪:那你干嘛对我们说这些鬼话?
Maggie: Then why are you telling us this nonsense?
开萝尔:因为这都是他的原话.听着,
Carol: Because that's what he told me.
我猜他一定是去干什么见不得人的事了,
Look, I know the truth is he's off doing something disgusting,
也许是非法的,也许他是去找那个瑞典女学生.
probably illegal, most likely involving that Swedish exchange student.
杰森:开萝尔谢谢你的帮助.
Jason: Ok.Thank you for your help.
开萝尔:我说对了.
Carol: You mean it?
麦琪:不,他是要你出去.
Maggie: No.He means leave the room.
开萝尔:好吧,听着,
Carol: Fine.Look, I just want you both to know, though,
我只想告诉你们,要是你们决定惩罚他,我一定会举双手赞成.
however you decide to punish him, I'm solidly behind you.
麦琪:杰森我简直想哭了,他竟然会不去面试.
Maggie: Jason, I am going to scream.He skipped his audition.
杰森:我还以为他热爱戏剧呢.
Jason: I thought he was serious about drama.
开萝尔:我发表意见,我认为对他要狠狠的惩罚一下.
Carol: And for the record, I do think he should be severely punished.
杰森:谢谢,快出去吧.
Jason: Thank you.Get out!
麦琪:我还记得那天他演完戏高兴的样子,
Maggie: Oh, I remember that look in his eyes after his first play.
连我都非常感动.
Boy, he had me convinced.
杰森:我也是,
Jason: Yea, me too.I remember when we saw him backstage.
我记得我在后台找到他的时候,我看到他的眼睛里充满了泪水,
He almost had tears in his eyes.
不过你看有没有这种可能.
He was You don't suppose it would be possible...
麦琪:哦,我绝不相信他是去了百老汇.
Maggie: Oh, don't tell me you believe this crazy Broadway story?
杰森:是不太可能,不过...
Jason: Well, not exactly but I just...
麦琪:不过,哦,不,你这个不过专家又来了.
Maggie: But?Oh, no.It's the famous Jason Seaver ,but.
杰森:怎么了?
Jason: Pardon me?
麦琪:杰森就算他是去了百老汇,他也是逃学了.
Maggie: Jason, even if he went to Broadway, he still cut school!
杰森:说得对,不过你有没有特别的禁止过他,不许他去百老汇呢.
Jason: Yes, but did you ever specifically forbid him to be in a Broadway play?
麦琪:这倒没有,不过.
Maggie: Well, no, but...
杰森:你没有禁止,我也一样.
Jason: Well, there you are!Neither did I!
麦琪:杀人放火的事,我们对他也没有禁止过啊?
Maggie: But we never specifically forbid him to blow up building's either.
杰森:他想去百老汇演出,也不是件坏事.
Jason: So, we're lucky he's only trying out for a Broadway play.
如果他真的去了他是有理由的.
And if that is what he did, then he did for a reason.
也许这次他确实是下定了决心,
He did it because for the first time in his life he really feels like
想轰轰烈烈的干出一番事业来,这并不是一件什么坏事.
following through with something, which isn't necessarily bad.
麦琪:说得对.
Maggie: Well, no, but...
杰森:去百老汇演出是需要胆量的,这一点是很不容易.
Jason: This audition would take a lot of guts and very little common sense.
麦琪:好吧,就算这样,不过对这种情况.
Maggie: Ok, that's Mike alright, but I still think...
杰森:对这种情况还是加以惩罚的是吗?
Jason: And is that something we really ought to punish?
麦琪:你意思是说我们不希望迈克翘课,
Maggie: So, you're saying we should hope that Mike didn't lie to us and
是为了到外面去胡搞?
cut school to wastetime.
而希望他翘课,
We should hope that Mike lied to us and cut school to take his chance
是为了上百老汇去参加面试.
on Broadway?
杰森:对,基本是这样.
Jason: Yea, that's about it.
麦琪:你同不同意应该罚他.
Maggie: But you agree we should punish him?
杰森:完全同意.不过马上带他上馆子.
Jason: Absolutely.But then we should take him out for dinner.
迈克:知道么,咱俩出了大洋相.
Mike: You know, you couldn't be more wrong.
莫妮卡:我可没说一句话.
Monica: I haven't said anything.
迈克:要是你跟我一起进去,
Mike: Well, maybe I wouldn't have made such a fool out of myself if you
我也许不会出这种洋相.
had gone in there with me.
莫妮卡:迈克可是你……
Monica: Mike, we couldn't
迈克:我至少没有逃出来这就证明了我.
Mike: I mean, at least I didn't chicken out.I mean, I proved
莫妮卡:什么迈克,证明了什么?
Monica: What, Mike?What did you prove?
迈克:证明了我,我,好,我也在骗自己.
Mike: Well, that, that I'm kidding myself.
莫妮卡:咱俩全是在骗自己.
Monica: We've both been kidding ourselves.
迈克:幸亏我把驾驶执照取回来.
Mike: I just thank God I got my driver's license back!
教练:很好,很好,
Coach Luvok: Well, well, well.
很好.
If it isn't the kid who left me hanging like a piece of meat,
迈克这小子今天耍了我这个老教练,我被搞得焦头烂额的.
rotting and twisting in the sun.
迈克:嗨,教练.
Mike: Hi, Coach.
卢沃克教练:别跟我来这套,
Coach Luvok: Don't.Hi, Coach' me!
我今天狼狈的只想找一个洞钻进去.
You didn't have to sit through the night of the living dead auditions.
迈克:我实在是万分抱歉.
Mike: Look, I'm sorry I let you down.
卢沃克教练:迈克我之所以自告奋勇的导演这部臭戏,
Coach Luvok: Seaver, you were the only reason I volunteered to direct
全是因为有了你,
this stinking play and then you didn't even show up.
可你竟会突然失踪了,结果全体教师都在笑我这个傻瓜蛋,
Now I got the entire faculty lounge giving ten to one odds that I'm really
我恨不得找个地洞钻进去.
going to crash through the ol' outhouse floor with this one.
迈克:实在对不起,是我不好.
Mike: Like I said, I'm sorry I let you down!
卢沃克教练:到时候你又会来求我,求你教练,
Coach Luvok: Oh, oh.Next you'll be begging.Oh, please Coach.
求你另外再选一个日子面试好吗?
Please carry auditions over for another day.
迈克:不,不会这样.
Mike: No, I won't.
Coach Luvok: Don't tell me how to run this production, Seaver
通知已经贴出来了.
I'm carrying the auditions over for another day.Sign up sheets on stage.
迈克:哦,谢谢.
Mike: No, thanks.
卢沃克教练:别摆臭架子了,我的先生.
Coach Luvok: Don't use that language with me, mister.
迈克:我在演戏方面不会有什么前途,你懂吗?
Mike: Look, I've just kind of decided there's no future for me in acting,
回头见.
alright?So, see you later.
卢沃克教练:你站住,你给我站住,你站住,
Coach Luvok: Hold it!Hold it!I said, hold it!
你给我站住.要是你再不理我的话,
Geez, if I wanted to be ignored, I'd go home!Now, look, Seaver.
我就不干了.迈克我知道你准有心事,我只是想告诉你,
I know something's been bothering you.
我两只耳朵始终是打开着的,有心事尽管讲,
I just want you to know the doors to my ears are always open.
家庭的,学校的,甚至那方面的.
You can talk to me about anything.Home life, school, even S-E-X.
迈克:好吧,好吧,
Mike: Alright, alright.Look.
听着,我今天没来是到百老汇去参加面试了.
Today I went to New York to audition for a Broadway play.
教练:你疯了,像你这样的混小子还想进百老汇.
Coach Luvok: Are you nuts?You didn't stand a snowball's chance in Florida.
迈克:说实话我要是真行的话,
Mike: Well, look, you know, if I was good, really good,
我早就被录取了,可是我没有资格进百老汇,
I would've gotten that part!
我只能在中学里,
But I'm not good enough for Broadway,
在一个体育教练的导演下演演戏.哦,
I'm just good enough for some high school play with some P.E.
对不起.
coach as the director and boy am I sorry I just said that.
卢沃克教练:你完全不必为这句话向我道歉,
Coach Luvok: Hey, hey, hey.You don't have to apologize to me for what I am.
我在这儿是滥竽充数,
I'm just the guy they send in whenever they can't get a real teacher to
等他们找到合适的人我就滚蛋了.
do the job.
迈克:行了教练.
Mike: Hey, come on, coach.
卢沃克教练:迈克我来告诉你我是怎么来这儿的?
Coach Luvok: Hey, Seaver.Let me tell you a little story how I ended up here.
其实我这个人完全是我妈多生下来的.
You see, my mother never actually wanted another child.
迈克:那么你是不是因为还是在孩子的时候,
Mike: Wait.Is this one of those stories where you face some big challenge
就遭到了重大的挫折,
when you were a kid and you didn't cut it so that's how you ended up
结果才到这儿来教书的?
where you are today?
卢沃克教练:不,我是因为毕业时,在全班得了一个倒数第一.
Coach Luvok: No, I ended up here because I graduated last of my class.
迈克:原来如此啊!!
Mike: Oh.
卢沃克教练:我是怎么会得倒数第一的?
Coach Luvok: And you know why I graduated last of my class?
迈克:有点不太好回答.
Mike: Sure not gonna answer that one.
卢沃克教练:你真聪明,我自己也没想到我会来教书,
Coach Luvok: Very smart.
我要做职业球员,所以根本不念书,
You see, I never figured I was gonna be a teacher,
有一天来人招球员,
I was gonna play pro-ball, so I never studied.
当时我怎么样,我愣住了.
Well, one day the scout showed up.You know what, Seaver?I choked.
迈克:那么第二次来招球员,
Mike: And I bet you were so bummed that you made the mistake of giving
你大概吓得都不敢参加了吧?
up your football career.
卢沃克教练:不,我没有那样,
Coach Luvok: No, I didn't Seaver.
那一次我认为我的球打得相当的出色,
I went right back on that field the very next week.
招聘的在旁边悄悄地看着,
And the scout was out there again.But this time, I didn't know he was there.
我不知道他来了,结果呢我还是不行.
And you know what?I still stunk!
迈克:教练你说这是什么意思?
Mike: Coach, what's the point of this story?
卢沃克教练:意思是说我失败过,跟你今天一样,
Coach Luvok: The point is that I tried.Like you did today.
一个人出几次洋相并没有什么.
It doesn't make a difference that you made a fool out of yourself and
要是我坚持下去,
if I caved in every time I thought I'd make a fool out of myself,
也许我一辈子也不会出洋相,也不至于会到这儿来.
I wouldn't be where I am right now.
迈克:在哪?
Mike: And where's that?
卢沃克教练:到这个学校里来教书,还要跟你这个最有天才的人谈话,
Coach Luvok: Standing here with a chance to work with the most talented
我要上厕所了.迈克:下一次,下一次.
high school
kid I ever saw.I gotta go to the can. Mike: Next time.Next time